export const wingSpan = {
    question: "What is the length of the Boeing 737-800 wingspan with winglets?",
    answers: ["35.79 meters.", "36 meters", "34.65 meters.", "37.84 meters."],
    correct: "35.79 meters."
};

export const maxFlap = {
    question: "What is the maximum flap setting?",
    answers: ["Flaps 40.", "Flaps 30.", "Flaps 25.", "Flaps 45."],
    correct: "Flaps 40."
};
export const maximumPsi = {
    question: "What is the maximum differential pressure?",
    answers: ["9.1 psi.", "10 psi.", "8.25 psi.", "11 psi."],
    correct: "9.1 psi."
};

export const maximumStartEGT = {
    question: "What is the maximum EGT on engine start?",
    answers: ["725", "925", "950", "750"],
    correct: "725"

};

export const numberGenerators = {
    question: "How many generators are fitted on the 737-800?",
    answers: ["3", "2", "1", "4"],
    correct: "3"
};

export const minimumUseHeight = {
    question: "What is the minimum use height for using autopilot?",
    answers: ["158 ft.", "400 ft.", "500 ft.", "237 ft."],
    correct: "158 ft."
};

export const lowFuel = {
    question: "When does amber low fuel light illuminate? ",
    answers: ["Less than 907 kg.", "Less than 1001 kg.", "Less than 999 kg.", "Less than 1200 kg."],
    correct: "Less than 907 kg."
};

export const maximumFlap = {
    question: "Above which altitude should you not attempt to deploy flaps?",
    answers: ["20000 ft.", "25000 ft.", "23000 ft.", "27500 ft."],
    correct: "20000 ft."
};

export const trUnitInFlight = {
    question: "If a TR Unit illuminates in flight, what does it mean?",
    answers: ["TR units 2 and 3 failed.", "One of the 2 TR units have failed.", "TR unit 3 failed.", "All TR units have failed."],
    correct: "TR units 2 and 3 failed."
};
export const hydFluidQuantMax = {
    question: "What is the maximum hydraulic quantity that can be displayed?",
    answers: ["106%.", "100%.", "105%.", "97%."],
    correct: "106%."
};


export const allQuestions = [wingSpan, maxFlap, maximumPsi, maximumStartEGT, numberGenerators, minimumUseHeight, lowFuel, maximumFlap, trUnitInFlight, hydFluidQuantMax];